A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Developing Countries Program, Latin America and the Caribbean, Office Files of Jeffrey M. Puryear FA638
Rockefeller Archive Center
Ford Foundation records, Developing Countries Program, Latin America and the Caribbean, Office Files of Jeffrey M. Puryear
1979-1985
Rockefeller Archive Center
Puryear, Jeffrey
Ford Foundation
FA638
1.64 Cubic Feet
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Arrangement
Chronological
Biographical / Historical
Jeffrey Puryear worked for a number of years at the Ford Foundation. In 1977, he worked as a Program Advisor for the Foundation's Andes Region and the Southern Cone Program. He then became a Program Officer for the umbrella Latin America and Caribbean Program in 1978. Following a change in the Foundation's program organization, Puryear became a Program Officer in the Developing Country Programs Division. From 1985 to 1989, he served as the Foundation's Representative for the Andes Region and the Southern Cone and was based at the Lima, Peru office.
Puryear's post-Ford Foundation career has included his work for the Inter-American Dialogue. At the Inter-American Dialogue, he has served as a vice president for social policy, a co-director of the Program for Educational Revitalization in the Americas (PREAL), and a senior fellow in the Education Program. He earned a Ph.D. in comparative education from the University of Chicago.
Scope and Contents
Contains correspondence
- 1979 Chronological Correspondence, 1979 September-October (Box 1)
- 1979 Chronological Correspondence, 1979 November-December (Box 1)
- 1980 Chronological Correspondence, 1980 January-March (Box 1)
- 1980 Chronological Correspondence, 1980 April-June (Box 1)
- 1980 Chronological Correspondence, 1980 July-September (Box 1)
- 1980 Chronological Correspondence, 1980 October-December (Box 1)
- 1981 Chronological Correspondence, 1981 January-March (Box 1)
- 1981 Chronological Correspondence, 1981 April-June (Box 1)
- 1981 Chronological Correspondence, 1981 July-September (Box 1)
- 1981 Chronological Correspondence, 1981 October-December (Box 1)
- 1982 Chronological Correspondence, 1982 January-March (Box 1)
- 1982 Chronological Correspondence, 1982 April-June (Box 1)
- 1982 Chronological Correspondence, 1982 July-September (Box 1)
- 1982 Chronological Correspondence, 1982 October-December (Box 1)
- 1983 Chronological Correspondence, 1983 January-March (Box 1)
- 1983 Chronological Correspondence, 1983 April-June (Box 1)
- 1983 Chronological Correspondence, 1983 July-September (Box 1)
- 1983 Chronological Correspondence, 1983 October-December (Box 1)
- 1984 Chronological Correspondence, 1984 January-March (Box 1)
- 1984 Chronological Correspondence, 1984 April-June (Box 2)
- 1984 Chronological Correspondence, 1984 July-September (Box 2)
- 1984 Chronological Correspondence, 1984 September-December (Box 2)
- 1985 Chronological Correspondence, 1985 January-August (Box 2)